Mert Çetin Frontend Developer

mrtctn506@gmail.com

+(90) 537 641 27 37

https://github.com/mertcetiin

in www.linkedin.com/in/mertcetin-dev/

About

Since 2022, I am a self-motivated and enthusiastic software developer. I want to be a good player who pursues a common goal, makes the team great. I always strive to reach the highest possible standard.

Skills

Next.js	React	TypeScript	JavaScript	TailwindCSS Sa	ss Bootstrap	CSS
HTML	Figma	Git & GitHub	Firebase	Framer Motion	Material UI	Apexcharts

Experience

2024/08 – present	Frontend Developer Doğuş Teknoloji
2024/04	Frontend Developer Lusemta Yazılım
	I developed a panel management site using React, Vite, MUI (Material-UI) and Framer Motion.
2024/01 - 2024/02	Frontend Developer Freelance I developed a responsive and optimized website for my client using Next.js and Tailwind CSS.

Projects

Algoo 🖸

In this project, I played a significant role in developing a modern and impressive website for Algoo.

-Next.js, TypeScript, TailwindCss, Framer Motion

Mert.dev ☑

This project contains a Next.js application used to create my personal portfolio website.

-Next.js, TypeScript

Education

2024/09	Management Information Systems İstanbul University
2019 - 2021	Mechanical Technician Bursa Uludag University